Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009; 5739-001; 26.52 cubic feet 31 boxes
  - Series III: Contract Negotiations, 1950-2009 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43; 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
    - Subseries B: Contract Negotiations Part 2, 1952-2009 (Box-folder 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
      - Omega Industrial Contractors, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 28/18)
      - O'Neil Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 28/19)
      - O'Neil Electric, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 28/20)
      - Optical Communications & Installation (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 28/21)
      - Opus Electric LLC (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 28/22)
      - Opus Electric LLC (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 28/23)
      - Orca Electric Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 28/24)
      - Oree Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 28/25)
      - Oree Electric Northwest, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1986 (Box-folder 28/26)
      - O.S.A., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1994 (Box-folder 28/27)
      - Oslo Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1960-1990 (Box-folder 28/28)
      - Overlake Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 28/29)
      - Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 28/30)
      - Pacific Coast Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 28/31)
      - Pacific Coast Hemphill Oil Company Contract Negotiations, 1952-1976; 1993 (Box-folder 28/32)
      - Pacific Electric Builders, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 28/33)
      - Pacific Electric Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1965-1976; 1993-2005 (Box-folder 28/34)
      - Pacific Electric Company (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28/35)
      - Pacific Electric Company (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box-folder 28/36)
      - Pacific Electric Company (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 28/37)
      - Pacific Electrical Contractors, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 28/38)
      - Pacific Heating Oils Contract Negotiations, 1956, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 28/39)
      - Park View Associates (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 28/40)
      - Parrish Fiber & Copper Cabling, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 28/41)
      - Payne Electrical Contractors (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box-folder 28/42)
      - Pearson Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1989; 2005 (Box-folder 28/43)
      - Peart Sign Company Contract Negotiations, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 28/44)
      - Perea Electric Contract Negotiations, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 28/45)
      - Peterson-Capiral (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 28/46)
      - Peterson Electric Contract Negotiations, 1958-1986 (Box-folder 28/47)
      - Peterson Heating and Cooling Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box-folder 28/48)
      - PH Construction Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 28/49)
      - Photo & Sound Company Contract Negotiations, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 28/50)
      - Pietro's Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 28/51)
      - Pim Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 28/52)
      - P.K. Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 28/53)
      - Plateau Electrical Constructors, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2003 (Box-folder 28/54)
      - Plateau Electrical Constructors, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 28/55)
      - Poulsbo Electric Contract Negotiations, 1965-1981 (Box-folder 28/56)
      - Power City Construction, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 28/57)
      - Power Field Services (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 28/58)
      - Power Services, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box-folder 28/59)
      - Precision Air (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 28/60)
      - Precision Communications Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 28/61)
      - Precision Concrete Cutting (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 28/62)
      - PRIME (Marine) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 28/63)
      - Prism Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 28/64)
      - Pro Electrical, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 28/65)
      - Professional Electric and Consulting, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 28/66)
      - Pro Media (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 28/67)
      - Prospect Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 28/68)
      - PSER, INC. (Inside Wire) - Specialty Refrigeration Manufacturing Control & Installation Contract Negotiations, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 28/69)
      - PSF Mechanical, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1977-1994 (Box-folder 28/70)
      - Pt. Orchard Electric (Inside Wire & Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 28/71)
      - Puget Sound Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 28/72)
      - Puget Sound Refrigeration, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 28/73)
      - PUIandE, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 28/74)
      - Pure Tech (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 28/75)
      - P & W Enterprises, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 28/76)
      - The Quadrant Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1970 (Box-folder 28/77)
      - Quality Communications & Electronics, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1969 (Box-folder 28/78)
      - Quality Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 28/79)
      - Quality Electric Co. - Kenneth Nystrom and L. Henrickson Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 28/80)
      - Quality Electric and Service, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 28/81)
      - Queen City Alarm Service (Sound-Communication-Telephone Interconnect) Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 28/82)
      - Radiation Laboratories, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 28/83)
      - Rainier Electric Service Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 28/84)
      - Ramstead Electric Contract Negotiations, 1960-1975 (Box-folder 28/85)
      - Ratelco, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1961-1975 (Box-folder 28/86)
      - Raymond M. Hudson Electrical Contractor (Inside Wire & Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 28/87)
      - Ray's Electronic Service Contract Negotiations, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 28/88)
      - R.B. Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 28/89)
      - R-C Electric Contract Negotiations, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 28/90)
      - Reddick Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 28/91)
      - Red Hills Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 28/92)
      - Renton Electric Company, Inc., 1972-1983 (Box-folder 28/93)
      - Rick Bakker Quality Electric Plus (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 28/94)
      - Rose Electric Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 28/95)
      - Salish Construction Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 28/96)
      - Seattle Concrete Core Drilling (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 28/97)
      - Seattle Electric Works (Motor Shop) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 28/98)
      - Seattle Industrial (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 28/99)
      - Seattle Industrial (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28/100)
      - Sea-West Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 28/101)
      - Sefnco, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 29/1)
      - Sefnco, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box-folder 29/2)
      - S Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 29/3)
      - Sequim Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 29/4)
      - Sequoyah Corporation (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 29/5)
      - Sequoyah Corporation (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 29/6)
      - Service Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1980 (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Shin's Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 29/8)
      - Sid's Choice Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 29/9)
      - Sid's Choice Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 29/10)
      - Silver Eagle Electrical Contractors, Inc.(Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 29/11)
      - Silver Eagle Service Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 29/12)
      - Sinclair Control Corporation (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 29/13)
      - SNG Specialty Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 29/14)
      - SNG Specialty Construction, Inc. (9th District Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 29/15)
      - Snipes Electric Co. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 29/16)
      - SOS Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 29/17)
      - SPES Company, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 29/18)
      - Spirit Electric, LLC (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box-folder 29/19)
      - Star Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 29/20)
      - Stationary Power Services Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 29/21)
      - Stewart Electric and Supply (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 29/22)
      - Straits Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-2006 (Box-folder 29/23)
      - Sturgeon Electric Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 29/24)
      - Sun Contracting of Spokane Contract Negotiations, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 29/25)
      - Sun Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 29/26)
      - Sun Innovations (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 29/27)
      - Swater Ivan (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 29/28)
      - System Control Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 29/29)
      - Tabor Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 29/30)
      - Tabor Electric (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 29/31)
      - Tabor Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 29/32)
      - Tabor Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 29/33)
      - Target Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 29/34)
      - Target Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 29/35)
      - Target/Alpine Joint Venture (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 29/36)
      - TC Borden Underground, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 29/37)
      - T.C. Quinn Electric Co., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 29/38)
      - T.C. Quinn Electric & Mechanical Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2009 (Box-folder 29/39)
      - Techi-Cable, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 29/40)
      - Teem Ventures Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1982 (Box-folder 29/41)
      - Teldata System's Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 29/42)
      - Teleengineering, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 29/43)
      - Terrace Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box-folder 29/44)
      - Thai Am Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 29/45)
      - Thai Am Electric Co. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 29/46)
      - The Juice Company (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 29/47)
      - Third Avenue Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1964-1975 (Box-folder 29/48)
      - Third Avenue Television, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 29/49)
      - Thomas G. Brennan Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 29/50)
      - Thomas M. Thum Company Contract Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 29/51)
      - Thomas Services, Inc. (Oil Burner) Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 29/52)
      - Thrifty Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 29/53)
      - Thunderloin Electric Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 29/54)
      - Tice Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 29/55)
      - Tigard Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 29/56)
      - Times Publishers Contract Negotiations, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 29/57)
      - Titan Electric, Inc. F/K/A Nottingham Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 29/58)
      - Titan Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 29/59)
      - Todd Shipyards Corp. Contract Negotiations, 1970 (Box-folder 29/60)
      - Tomco Construction (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 29/61)
      - Totem Electric of Tacoma (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 29/62)
      - Totem Partners/Joint Venture Project (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994 (Box-folder 29/63)
      - Town & Country Electric Co., Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 29/64)
      - Tranquility Electric & General Construction Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 29/65)
      - Trans-Pacific, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 29/66)
      - Transworld Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 29/67)
      - Transworld Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 29/68)
      - Transworld Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 29/69)
      - Transworld Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 29/70)
      - Tri-County Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 29/71)
      - Trig Electric Construction Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 29/72)
      - Trig Electric Construction Co., Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 29/73)
      - Tri Star Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 29/74)
      - Tube Art Displays, Inc. Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 29/75)
      - Tube Art Displays, Inc. Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 29/76)
      - Trumball Electric Corp. Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 29/77)
      - Tukwila Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 29/78)
      - Tusk Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 29/79)
      - T.W. Davis Electrical Contractors (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 29/80)
      - T-Z Electrical Construction Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 29/81)
      - Udelhoven General, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 29/82)
      - Underground Distributing Lighting, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 29/83)
      - Underground Distributing Lighting, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 29/84)
      - UNICO Properties (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2007 (Box-folder 29/85)
      - United Administrators, Inc. (Box-folder 29/)
      - United Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 29/86)
      - United Electric Motors Contract Negotiations, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 29/87)
      - United Power, Contractors & Engineers, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 29/88)
      - Uni-T Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 29/89)
      - Unitek Systems (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 29/90)
      - University of Washington Contract Negotiations, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 29/91)
      - University Properties Contract Negotiations, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 29/92)
      - U.S. Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire & Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1982 (Box-folder 29/93)
      - U.S. Engineering Co. Contract Negotiations, 1978-1994 (Box-folder 29/94)
      - Vallejo Enterprises Co. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 30/1)
      - Valley Co-op (Oil Burner) Contract Negotiations, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 30/2)
      - Valley Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 30/3)
      - Valley Electric of Mount Vernon Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 30/4)
      - Valley Industrial (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 30/5)
      - Valley Industrial (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 30/6)
      - Vance Corporation Contract Negotiations, undated (Box-folder 30/7)
      - Vashon Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 30/8)
      - VECA Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 30/9)
      - VECA Electric Co., Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 30/10)
      - V.F.C., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2005 (Box-folder 30/11)
      - V.F.C., Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 30/12)
      - Viking Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1971-1995 (Box-folder 30/13)
      - Viking Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box-folder 30/14)
      - Viking Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 30/15)
      - Vision Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 30/16)
      - Vista Construction (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1986 (Box-folder 30/17)
      - V & V Construction (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 30/18)
      - Warburton Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1960-1989 (Box-folder 30/19)
      - War-Mur Electric Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 30/20)
      - Warne Electric & Appliance Service (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1960-1986 (Box-folder 30/21)
      - Warren's Electric Contract Negotiations, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 30/22)
      - Washington Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979-1992, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 30/23)
      - Washington Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 30/24)
      - Washington Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 30/25)
      - Washington State Convention & Trade Center and Washington State Convention & Trade Center Labor Council Contract Negotiations, 1988 (Box-folder 30/26)
      - Washington State Department of Labor & Industries (Electrical Inspectors) Contract Negotiations, 1980 (Box-folder 30/27)
      - Washington State Ferries (Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 30/28)
      - Watkins Electric Contract Negotiations, 1984 (Box-folder 30/29)
      - Watts Electric Service, Inc. F/K/A W.T. Watts, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 30/30)
      - W.D. Whinery, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 30/31)
      - Jim Wells Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1960-1989 (Box-folder 30/32)
      - Werner Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 30/33)
      - Werner Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box-folder 30/34)
      - West Coast Electric Company of Washington Contract Negotiations, 1955-1980 (Box-folder 30/35)
      - West Coast Electric Service (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/36)
      - West Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 30/37)
      - Western Environmental, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 30/38)
      - Westfire Coastal, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 30/39)
      - West Fuel Company Contract Negotiations, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 30/40)
      - Westgate Electric Contract Negotiations, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 30/41)
      - Westlake Fuels, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 30/42)
      - West Seattle Furnace Sales Contract Negotiations, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 30/43)
      - West Star Engineering, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 30/44)
      - R.D. White Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 30/45)
      - White Light Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 30/46)
      - Whitrock Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 30/47)
      - Willamette Electrical Construction Co. Contract Negotiations, 1972 (Box-folder 30/48)
      - Williamson Laboratories, Inc. (Sound-Intercommunication-Telephone Interconnect) Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 30/49)
      - Wilskey Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 30/50)
      - Wilson Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 30/51)
      - W-K Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 30/52)
      - W.L. Tadlock (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 30/53)
      - Wor-Ell Custom Lighting Contract Negotiations, 1969-1985 (Box-folder 30/54)
      - W.R.G. Electric (Inside Wire & Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 30/55)
      - W.R.G. Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 30/56)
      - W.R.G. Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 30/57)
      - W.R.G. Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 30/58)
      - Wright, Inc. Electrical Contractors (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 30/59)
      - Wright Schuchart Harbor Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 30/60)
      - Wyatt Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 30/61)
      - Yansen Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1960-2967 (Box-folder 30/62)
      - Zephyr Communications Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 30/63)
      - Zephyr Communications Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 30/64)
  - Series IV: Office Files, 1940-1991 (Box-folder 4/2; 5/3; 5/8; 7/7; 20/2-20/4; 20/8; 20/18; 20/20; 20/22; 31/1-31/10)
    Series IV documents the day-to-day procedures at the office of Local 46, including by-laws, dispatch records and correspondence. In addition, Subseries F: IBEW Bugs displays the evolution of the national IBEW Bugs and Subseries G: Proclamations highlights the support of Local 46 by the local government.